Oh.
Where are you two kids
going?
Why are you here?
To save you, your master
is fighting the ten demon soldiers led by Jin Wang.
But there are only three of them.
I think they are just throwing an egg against a rock.
Lady Tu sent me to guard you
just in case.
As expected,
you almost escaped.
And you even want to take her medicine ingredient away.
Master really came to save me.
Wait a minute.
Three people.
Also Sister Gesang and Lord Hu San.
My master is a deity.
Whatever Tu Goddess,
in front of my master, she's just like you,
a wild village demon.
Reckless thing.
Since your master is here anyway,
I'll kill you right now
so your foul mouth can never speak again.
Ancestor,
leave this guy to me.
You go deal with Tu Luohua.
If we don't get rid of her,
none of us will have a good life.
Spirits of heaven and earth,
spanning the vast universe,
reaching everywhere.
Flash!
Do you think
you can stop me?
I can't stop you,
but the immortal spirit within me
might be able to.
Immortal spirit?
I didn't want to use this move.
I'm afraid of being possessed by the master within.
But now,
it's the only way.
Watch closely.
This move
is going to be very cool.
Let's see
how long you can keep up this appearance.
Immortal.
Immortals are exactly what I slay.
I didn't expect
you to have some skills.
Bullying a child
is not a real skill.
Sister Gesang,
you didn't lie to me.
You came to save me.
Of course I keep my word.
Another one coming to die.
Cut the crap,
you wild demon.
Golden Immortal.
I have searched so hard for you.
You have cultivated for thousands of years.
If you devote yourself to cultivation,
your ascension is within reach.
Why bother
wreaking havoc
and harming the people?
Ascend to immortality?
How can the chance to become an immortal be gained easily?
You once guarded Sanshan Stream,
so you naturally understand this.
Why do you deceive me like this?
If so,
you should know.
Anyone ascending to immortality
must first pass the Three Mountain Streams.
They must sever desires to return to the void,
and cut off attachments to merge with the Dao,
before they can embark on the immortal path.
What a 'sever desires to return to the void and cut off attachments to merge with the Dao'.
Are immortals truly free from all desires?
If that's true,
why did the Golden Immortal feel compassion for my sister?
Your sister,
Bai Jingqing.
What a hypocritical supreme immortal.
That's right.
Jingqing is my sister.
She cultivated hard for a thousand years.
Even though she had proven Hunyuan at that time,
it was no match for the lingering attachment you left her.
She just had feelings for you,
and it made me end up like this.
Since you left that thread of love when you met her,
she became obsessed with it.
Because of you, she severed all emotions and left me.
You forcefully turned my carefree long road
into a disaster of human suffering.
The Way of Heaven has its duty.
Reincarnation has its order.
In this world,
good things are hard to perfect.
Why bother with the rules of Heaven?
With the Immortal Lord by my side,
why sit withered on a cold cliff
guarding those pedantic old rules?
This immortal path
requires ascetic cultivation.
Only by perceiving and understanding within
can anger and ignorance dissipate
and the mind become clear.
If you delusionally think of taking side paths,
it will eventually be like fishing for the moon in the water.
If one can prove the Dao and become an immortal,
who cares whether the path is orthodox or not?
Golden Immortal, you are truly heartless.
If you share your divine power with me,
I will let your friends go immediately.
I won't hold you back afterwards.
You are an immortal.
This is effortless for you.
If you insist on refusing,
I will refine them all into Nine-Turn Soul-Restoring Pills.
If you refuse to be a vessel,
then perish along with them.
How do you know
you can definitely beat me?
Your immortal roots have been severed.
The way you are now,
how could I not beat you?
Ping Jie Qiang Hai Hui.